viralrecall.com 2016-11-04

# Privacy Policy – VIRALrecall

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the www.ViralRecall.com and ViralRecall.com and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to ViralRecall.com include www.ViralRecall.com and ViralRecall.com. The ViralRecall.com website is an entertainment based site. By using the ViralRecall.com website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

**Collection of your Personal Information**

We do not collect personally identifiable information from our users. We may gather personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by ViralRecall.com. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the ViralRecall.com website.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through ViralRecall.com’s public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.

ViralRecall.com encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from ViralRecall.com so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. ViralRecall.com is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the ViralRecall.com website.

**Use of Cookies**

The ViralRecall.com website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize ViralRecall.com pages, or register with ViralRecall.com site or services, a cookie helps ViralRecall.com to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same ViralRecall.com website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the ViralRecall.com features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the ViralRecall.com services or websites you visit.

**Security of your Personal Information**

ViralRecall.com secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.

**Children Under Thirteen**

ViralRecall.com does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

**Opt-Out & Unsubscribe**

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from ViralRecall.com by contacting us here:

– Email: info@viralrecall.com

**Changes to this Statement**

ViralRecall.com will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. ViralRecall.com encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how ViralRecall.com is protecting your information.

**Contact Information**

ViralRecall.com welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that ViralRecall.com has not adhered to this Statement, please contact ViralRecall.com at: info@viralrecall.com

_________________

Los Angeles, California 90027

Email Address: info@viralrecall.com

**Effective as of September 01, 2015**
